[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以说我们忍不住添加了一些新的语法。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So saying that we couldn't resist adding some new syntax.
我们做的不是太多
We did it not too much and
我会警告你，在IE 9之前的浏览器中，所有这些都是致命的错误，
I'll warn you all of these are fatal errors in browsers before IE 9,
所以，如果你还在使用IE8，请忽略以下内容。
so if you're still on IE 8 please ignore the following.
因此我们在Object文字中添加了尾随逗号，
So we added trailing commas to object literals,
这是没有用的，我不建议你使用它。
which is not useful, I don't recommend you use it.
我们这样做的原因是因为我们修复了尾随逗号的工作方式
The reason we did that was because we fixed the way trailing commas worked in
数组文字。
array literals.
原来数组总是允许悬挂的逗号，但是
It turns out arrays always allowed that dangling comma but
他们对它的意思有不同意见。
they disagreed on what it meant.
在某些浏览器上，该数组的长度为2。
On some browsers that array would have a length of two.
在IE浏览器上，它的长度为3。
On IE browsers it had a length of three.
当你有这种差异时，可能会发生错误，所以我们将其更改为
When you have that kind of disparity bugs can happen so we changed it so
该规则现在将忽略悬挂的逗号，因此
the rule is now the dangling comma is ignored so
每个人都会同意它有两个长度。
everybody will agree that it has a length of two.
我们修复了一个可怕的保留字策略。
We fixed a terrible reserved word policy.
JavaScript最初的保留字策略说
JavaScript's original reserved word policy said that
在名称位置、对象文字或对象中不能有保留字
you could not have a reserved word in name position, in an object literal or
在点位置，没有理由这样做。
in dot position and there's is no reason for that.
我们修好了。
We fixed that.
所以现在所有黄色的东西都是错误的，现在一切都好了。
So everything that's yellow now used to be an error, that's all now okay.
所以这很好。
So that's good.
事实上，JSON需要将其引号引起来的原因是
In fact the reason that JSON requires quotes around its
名称是因为ES3中的这个设计问题。
names was because of this design problem in ES3.
我们添加了getter和setter。
We added getters and setters.
这些是访问器属性，因此当您去检索值时
These are accessor properties, so that when you go to retrieve a value
从对象或转到将值存储到对象中，而不是函数中
from an object or go to store a value into an object, instead a function
将被调用，它将使用您的值或返回值。
will be called which will either consume your value or return a value.
这就允许了一些新的编程形式。
And that allows some new forms of programming.
这里我们得到了一个具有摄氏度属性的温度构造函数
So here we've got a temperature constructor which has a celsius property
还有一处华氏房产。
and a fahrenheit property.
您可以读取其中任何一个，也可以设置其中任何一个。
You can read either one and you can set either one.
你不知道它是如何工作的，但它只是工作。
You don't know how it works but it just works.
这是一件非常漂亮的事情。
That's a pretty nifty thing.
现在看来，你可以用这个做一些非常愚蠢的事情，因为
Now turns out you can do some really stupid stuff with this because
如果你正确使用这些方法，那么这些方法将是非常有限的，
if you use this correctly, then these methods will be very limited,
在他们做的事情上非常有限，但对他们没有实际的限制。
very restricted in what they do, but there is no actual restriction on them.
他们什么都能做。
They can do anything.
他们可以改变世界上的一切，所以你可以
They can change everything in the world and so you can
只需读取对象的属性，就可以使事情在那里发生。
simply by reading a property of an object you can cause things to happen over there.
我不建议你这么做，因为这很愚蠢。
I don't recommend you do that because it's stupid.
我肯定有人会这么做，他们会，
I'm sure somebody is gonna do that and they're gonna,
我敢打赌，没有人认为你可以做到这一点，并且会去做到这一点。
I bet nobody thought that you could do that, and will go and do that.
我们确实考虑过这一点，只是希望没有人这样做。
We actually did think about that, just hoping nobody does that.
前面，我们讨论了多行字符串文字，
Earlier, we talked about the multiline string literals,
我仍然认为这是个错误。
I still think this was a mistake.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这太棒了。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: This is great.
所以它过去是无穷大的，NaN和undefined都不是常量，
So it used to be infinity, NaN and undefined were not constants,
它们是全局变量，这意味着您可以更改它们。
they were global variables, which meant you could change them.
你可以说今天无穷大是五，让我们看看会发生什么。
You could say today infinity is five, let's see what happens.
&gt；&gt；[笑]&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我知道这种安全性
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I know that security
专家们非常担心有人重新定义未定义，并且
experts were very worried about someone redefining undefined, and
那会有什么后果。
what the consequences of that could be.
我不知道因此而发生的任何利用行为，但是
I'm not aware of any exploits that actually happened as a result of that, but
这是一件令人担忧的事情。
it is something that was worried about.
因此它们现在是只读变量。
So they are now read only variables.
所以[声音]现在是固定的。
So [SOUND] now that's fixed.
我们修复了parseInt
We fixed parseInt so
当第一个字符为零时，它不再默认为八进制。
that it no longer defaults to octal when the first character is zero.
无论如何，我还是建议加入基数论证，但是
I still recommend putting in the radix argument anyway but
至少默认行为没有以前那么糟糕。
at least the least the default behavior is not nearly as bad as it had been.
正则表达式文字现在将生成一个新的正则表达式
Regular expression literals now will produce a new regular expression
对象，因此它们的工作方式与函数相同。
object every time they're evaluated, so they work the same way that functions do.
我们这样做的原因是，最初编译器只会创建
The reason we did that, originally the compiler would only create
每个正则表达式文字对应一个正则表达式对象。
one regular expression object for each regular expression literal.
问题是，它们包含国家。
And the problem with that is, that they contain state.
例如，它们包含最后一个，
For example they contain a last,
最后一个位置或最后一个位置，有人记得吗？
what was it last position or last, anybody remember?
EXEC用来记住最后一场比赛发生在哪里的东西。
The thing that exec uses to remember where the last match happened.
没人知道？
No one knows?
无论如何，这里有一个变量，如果每个人都分享它，
Anyway, there's this variable that's in there which if everybody is sharing it,
那么你不能让多个高管发生，因为他们会干扰
then you can't have multiple execs happening because they'll interfere with
所以我们解决了这个问题。
each other so we fixed that.
这太糟糕了，所以我之前告诉过您对象函数。
This was awful, so I told you earlier about the object function.
每次创建对象时都会调用它，
It gets called every time you make an object,
每次创建数组时都会调用数组函数。
and the array function gets called every time you make an array.
结果是你可以用你的函数替换这些函数，所以
It turns out you could replace those functions with your function so
每次有人创建对象或数组时都会调用您。
you get called every time someone makes an object or an array.
这是一个巨大的安全违规，对吧？
And that's a huge security violation, right?
您不希望某些代码能够接管这些东西，所以
You don't want some code to be able to take those things over, so
规范现在会说好像是通过原始的目标函数或数组
the specification will now say as if by the original object function or array
函数，您仍然可以替换它们，但不会遇到安全风险。
function that you can still replace them but you don't get the security hazard.
我很高兴地报告，JSON是世界上最受欢迎的数据交换格式，
I'm happy to report that JSON, the world's best loved data interchange format,
现在已内置到语言中。
is now built into the language.
因此，我们得到了一个JSON对象，它提供了一个parse函数和一个stringify函数。
So we've got a JSON object that provides a parse function and a stringify function.
那些名字都是我的错，完全是我的错。
Those names are my fault, completely my fault.
我可能应该说编码或解码，或者类似的东西，但是
I probably should have said encode or decode, or something like that, but
我没有。
I didn't.
所以我们被困在那里了，所以，不客气。
So we're stuck with those, so, you're welcome.
&gt；&gt；[笑]&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：如果你正在使用
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: If you're using
json2.js那么它的工作方式完全相同，
json2.js then it works exactly the same,
除了json2.js知道如果有内置的话应该让路，
except json2.js knows to get out of the way if built in one is there,
所以它会变得更快，这就是你想要的。
so it'll just get faster which is what you want.